<resources>
    <string name="finaxis">Finaxis</string>
    <string name="discover_the_power_of_seamless">Discover the power of seamless banking. We're excited to help you manage your finances effortlessly. Let’s get started!</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="get_started_by_sharing">Get Started by Sharing Your Details</string>
    <string name="signup_description">To continue, we need your name and phone number. This information will be used to set up your account and communicate important updates.</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome Back</string>
    <string name="signIn_description">Welcome back! Please enter your phone number to sign in and enjoy our services.</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="cardNumber">Card Number</string>
    <string name="cardPassword">Card Password</string>
    <string name="kyc_intro_title">Just a few steps to your account</string>
    <string name="kyc_intro_description">To ensure a safe and secure experience, we need to verify your identity. Please follow the steps to complete the KYC process.</string>
    <string name="kyc_first_step_title">Step 1: Choose Your Bank</string>
    <string name="kyc_first_step_description">To get started with your KYC process, please select your bank from the list below. This step helps us tailor the verification process to your specific bank's requirements.</string>
    <string name="kyc_second_step_title">Step 2: Enter phone number</string>
    <string name="kyc_second_step_description">To complete your KYC process, please enter the phone number associated with your selected bank account. This helps us ensure that your account information is accurate and up-to-date.</string>
    <string name="kyc_third_step_title">Step 3: Enter your username</string>
    <string name="kyc_third_step_description">
    You're almost there! please enter a unique username below. This step helps other people reach you based on your username and ensures your account is securely verified and ready for use.
    </string>
    <string name="kyc_fourth_step_title">Final Step: Enter your card info</string>
    <string name="kyc_fourth_step_description">To complete your verification, please provide your card details below. This final step ensures the security and authenticity of your account.</string>

</resources>